Inventory of the Paul N. McCloskey papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Washington, D.C. office (Box 279)
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 339)
    - "8900--Department file/Casework--ERDA (Energy Research and Development Administration)" to "9175--Department file/Casework--NASA (National Aeronautics and Space Administration)--Informatics,", 1977
    - "20030--Energy--Nuclear power study Rayfield" to "20077--Energy--Carter energy plan information,", 1980 (Box 340)
    - "13000--Business--Semiconductor industry" to "14010--Civil rights--Abortion information,", 1979-1980 (Box 341)
  - Staff members' files--Michele Farrar, 1977-1979 (Box 342)
    - National Maritime Council (NMC) Transportation Institute
    - MARAD (Maritime Administration)/NMC investigation and some cargo preference
    - Sieverts/Laos
    - Food aid to Laos
    - Patty Hearst
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 343)
    - "8605--Department file/Casework--Academies--Initial nomination request" to "8880--Department file/Casework--Sunnyvale Aircraft and Crash School Defense/A.F.,", 1977-1980
    - "17596--Defense--National youth service" to "17615--Defense--SALT II--Con,", 1975-1980 (bulk 1980) (Box 344)
    - "10000--Aging" to "13000--Business--Briefing for National Semiconductor 10/20,", 1980 (Box 345)
  - Staff members' files--Rebecca Cook (Box 346)
    - Population: Depo-Provera, contraception, sex education, Select Committee on Population, Pete's response to Teitlebaum memo, responses to Scheuer letter, Greep report, 1977-1979
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 347)
    - "21106--Environment--Rare II" to "21121--Environment--Stanislaus Huey Johnson testimony,", 1979-1980
    - "17000--Defense. Files on military manpower and registration for military service, 1979-1980 (Box 348)
    - "18500--Economy" to "19505--Education--Department of Education,", 1979-1980
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 349)
    - Campaign finances, 1976
    - Campaign legal interpretations
    - Reports of receipts and expenditures for a candidate, 1974-1977
    - Reports of receipts and expenditures for a committee, 1972-1974
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1978-1979 (Box 350)
    - Alcatraz Island, Channel Islands
    - Bilateral shipping
    - American sea power
    - New maritime policy
    - Coast Guard and navigation
    - McCloskey Coast Guard authorization
    - Committee budget
    - Conneaut Harbor
    - Construction differential subsidy
    - Corpus Christi oil spill
    - Controlled substances
    - Cotton club
    - Tom Crowley
    - Dumbarton quarry
    - Federal Maritime Commission
    - Fishermen's Protective Act
    - Finnish ice breakers
    - Fortune articles
    - Freight forwarders
    - Great Lakes basin
    - High seas and inland waters
    - International trade reorganization
    - Kings Point
    - Lease sale #53--California
    - Longshoremen's Association
    - Maritime appropriations
    - Snyder amendment--Maritime Administration authorization
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 351)
    - "9255--Department file/Casework--State Department--General" to "9350--Department file/Casework--Treasury--Internal Revenue Service,", 1978-1980
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1976-1978 (Box 352)
    - Aquaculture
    - Antarctic flora and fauna
    - Chesapeake Bay Research Coordination Act
    - Council on Environmental Quality
    - Endangered species
    - Coastal zone management
    - Elephants, marine mammals
    - Finnish or foreign-built icebreakers
    - Fishermen's Protective Act
    - Fisheries authorization
    - Inter-American Tropical Tuna Commission
    - Fish and Wildlife Improvement Act
    - Indian rights
    - Nongame fish and wildlife
    - International whaling conference
    - Ammunition tax bill, H.R. 9067
  - Sponsor/Cosponsor bill file. H.R. 1139 - H.R. 13923 (with gaps), and concurrent resolutions, etc., 1977-1978 (Box 353)
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 354)
    - "28000--Religion" to "31160--Transportation--Trucking deregulation,", 1979-1980
    - "9345--Department file/Casework--Customs Department reform/Department of Treasury" to "9375--Department file/Casework--Trade Special Representative, 1979-1980. (Box 355)
      Bulk is "9365--Department file/Casework--Veterans Administration--Palo Alto VA Hospital (Police)"
    - "13030--Bottler's bill,", 1979 (Box 356)
    - "20080--Energy--Oil price decontrol--Pro" to "22520--Federal government--Saccharin--Cyclamate ban,", 1979
    - "16170--Congress--Lobby Registration Act--Pro" to "17596--Defense--National Youth Service--Pro,", 1979 (Box 357)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1976-1979 (Box 358)
    - Defense authorization
    - U.S.-flag merchant marine
    - World Trade Club roster
    - Competitive rate program--Movement of military household goods
    - Pacific Maritime Association annual report, 1976
    - SOSUS cable ship requirements
    - Law of the sea, 1975
    - Liner shipping in the U.S. trades
    - Sea-Land Service, Inc.
    - Competition in North Atlantic container trade
    - Ocean shipping
    - Deep seabed mining
    - Soviet liner fleet
  - Miscellany
    - Family planning publications
    - Republican National Committee presidential accountability report
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1976-1978 (Box 359)
    - Marine fire-fighting
    - Foreign Affairs article
    - Foreign freight forwarders
    - Deep water port application of Seadock
    - Fish processing
    - FBI port investigation
    - FMC rate increase
    - Controlled carrier bill
    - Novachek debate
    - Crowley Maritime Corporation
    - Defense authorization
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 360)
    - "7252--Invitations--Washington accept" to "7313--Equipment/Orders--Official expenses account,", 1977
    - "14110--Civil rights--Gay rights" to "19560--Education--Vocational education,", 1977 (Box 361)
    - "25590--Labor--Labor unions general statement" to "28010--Religion--Moonies,", 1979 (Box 362)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1977-1978 (Box 363)
    - Pacific Far East Lines
    - Panama Canal
    - Pooling agreements
    - Port caucus
    - Preventing collisions at sea
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 364)
    - "7007--Personal--Book sent (Truth/Untruth)" to "7458--Requests--GPO request (paid),", 1977
  - Sponsor/Cosponsor bill file. H.R. 1656 - H.R. 14163 (with gaps), including joint resolutions, etc., 1977 (Box 365)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1977-1978 (Box 366)
    - Correspondence
    - Australian Shipping Act
    - Barba Negra appeal
    - German bus shipments on Soviet vessels
    - Capital construction
    - Cargo containers--Uniform requirements
    - Cargo preference
    - Carter's campaign promises
    - Budget for 1978
    - Controlled carrier
  - Government Operations Committee file, 1975-1978 (Box 367)
    - Office of consumer representation
    - Consumer protection agency
    - Nickel campaign
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 368)
    - "20000--Energy--General letters" to "20195--Energy--Energy tax,", 1977
    - "7502--Thank you--Sent" to "8506--Washington visitor--Tour request complete,", 1977 (Box 369)
    - "8800--Department file/Casework--Agriculture Department--Forest Service" to "8899--Department file/Casework--Department of Energy,", 1977
    - "4500--Member of Congress,", 1977 (Box 370)
    - "7004--Personal--Friends" to "7230--Intern inquiry--Intern summer reject,", 1977
    - "21000--Environment" to "22680--Health--Medical malpractice,", 1977 (Box 371)
    - "10000--Aging--General" to "14100--Civil rights--Freedom of expression--Con,", 1977 (Box 372)
  - Government Operations Committee file, 1977-1978 (Box 373)
    - Full committee general
    - Information and Individual Rights Subcommittee
    - Other subcommittees general
    - Cost accounting standards board
    - Federal government reorganization
    - Garrison diversion project
    - McCloskey Freedom of Information Act request
    - Obey Commission--Congressional reform
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 374)
    - "22690--Health--Medicare/Medicaid reform" to "24650--International relations--Law of the Sea conference general statement,", 1977
  - Government Operations Committee file, 1976-1977 (Box 375)
    - Government in the sunshine
    - Privacy
    - Freedom of information
    - Van pooling
    - Consumer protection
    - Office of consumer representation
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1976-1978 (Box 376)
    - Oceanography Subcommittee--Deep seabed mining
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 377)
    - "9160--Department file/Casework--Labor--Office of Workers' Compensation" to "9370--Department file/Casework--White House,", 1977
  - Printed matter. Congressional Record reprints about gun control (Box 378)
    - Jim Moore's open letter to the Congress, 1981 February 2
    - Lowenstein testimonial dinner, 1981 March 13
  - Briefing books, 1979-1981 (Box 379)
    - Busing--The Congress
    - Busing--The Courts
    - Gay rights
    - Busing--The Congress (Box 380)
    - Busing--The Courts
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 381)
    - "24520--International relations--China relations" to "24650--International relations--American business in South Africa,", 1980
    - "24635--International relations--American Near East refugee aid" to "24730--International relations--Namibia,", 1979-1980 (Box 382)
    - "24677--International relations--Pakistan--Ali Bhutto case (1978)" to "25570--Labor--Full Employment and Balanced Growth Act--Pro,", 1979 (Box 383)
  - Briefing books. Middle East, 1973-1978
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 384)
    - "22530--Health--Drug abuse" to "24670--International relations--Mideast general statement,", 1978-1979
  - Briefing books (Box 385)
    - Middle East--Press, 1970-1980
    - Nuclear nonproliferation, 1981 June 26
    - Mideast press, 1981-1982
  - Printed matter. Hearings and committee prints relating to Southeast Asia, 1968-1971
  - Briefing books (Box 386)
    - Southern Africa--Press, 1979, 1981
    - Mideast, 1970
    - Persian Gulf: Worth fighting for?
    - Israeli-Palestinian conflict, 1981
    - Immigration, 1981
    - National youth service, 1980
    - Defense budget cuts, 1982 (Box 387)
    - Saudi peace plan, 1981
    - Immigration policy, volume 2, 199
    - Islam summary, 1981
    - Sixteenth annual Anglo-North American parliamentary conference on Africa, 1980
    - Pakistan's nuclear capability
    - Mideast, 1980 (Box 388)
    - Nuclear proliferation, 1981
    - Immigration policy, volume 1, 1981
  - Printed matter
    - Hearings on government classification of private ideas, 4 volumes, 1980
    - NATO (North Atlantic Treaty Organization) fact book
    - National survey of veterans, 1979
    - Survey of race relations in South Africa, 1979
  - Briefing books (Box 389)
    - Laos refugees (AID data), 1970
    - War crimes, 1971
    - Terrorism, 1976
    - Campaign Harris issues, 1976
    - Press releases, 1975
    - "Dear Colleague" letters, 1974
    - Presidential war powers, 1971
  - Printed matter. Hearing and committee print on Southeast Asia, 1969-1970
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 390)
    - "8785--Department file/Casework--Action" to "8965--Department file/Casework--Federal Energy Administration,", 1981
    - "8970--Department file/Casework--Federal Communications Commission" to "9105--Department file/Casework--Justice Department general,", 1980-1981 (Box 391)
    - "9110--Department file/Casework--Justice--FBI" to "9375--Department file/Casework--White House--Special Trade Representative,", 1981 (Box 392)
    - "10000--Aging" to "10520--Agriculture--Farm price supports letters,", 1981
    - "10520--Agriculture--Peanut price supports" to "12030--Banking and currency--Federal Reserve Board,", 1981 (Box 393)
    - "12070--Banking and currency--Banking system reform" to "13077--Business--PNM (P. N. McCloskey) testimony (1981 June 16)," (Box 394)
    - "13077--Business--Letter to Cap Weinberger" to "14010--Civil rights--Abortion--Pro,", 1979-1981 (Box 395)
    - "14020--Civil rights--Abortion--Con" to "14060--Civil rights--Busing--Con,", 1981 (Box 396)
    - "14060--Civil rights--Busing--Judge Egly's order of 1980 August 25" to "15130--Communications-- Transborder data flow,", 1981 (Box 397)
    - "16000--Congress" to "17030--Crime and justice--Criminal code returns,", 1980-1981 (Box 398)
    - "21155--Environment--Outer continental shelf (OCS) minerals leasing and OCS lease--Sale #53 (California),", 1981 (Box 399)
    - "11088--Animal welfare--Medfly information,", 1981
    - "17052--Crime and justice--Criminal code reform contacts" to "17095--Crime and justice--Legal services corporation,", 1981 (Box 400)
    - "17095--Crime and justice--Legal services corporation" to "17500--Defense--GAO (Government Accounting Office) report--Managing battlefield intelligence data,", 1980-1981 (Box 401)
    - "17500--Defense--McCloskey military history" to "17596--Defense--Military manpower procurement--Richard Cooper (1980),", 1980-1981 (Box 402)
    - "17596--Defense--Department of State/National service" to "18520--Economy and budget-- Budget--General,", 1980-1981 (Box 403)
    - "18530--Economy and budget--Deficit spending--Pro" to "18590--Economy and budget--Wage and price controls,", 1981 (Box 404)
  - Briefing book. Budget, 1981
  - Printed matter
    - Arms control
    - Committee hearing on ocean dumping of radioactive waste off the Pacific coast, 1980
    - Committee hearing on presidential commission on national service and national commission on volunteerism, 1980
  - Miscellany
    - Military service information
    - Joint economic committee conference information, 1980
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 405)
    - "18600--Economy and budget--Wage and price controls--Con" to "20035--Energy--Nuclear waste disposal,", 1980-1981
    - "20036--Energy--Farallon Islands nuclear dump" to "20175--Energy--Synthetic fuels,", 1981 (Box 406)
    - "20178--Energy--Oil shale" to "21150--Environment--Outer continental shelf,", 1981 (Box 407)
    - "21155--Environment--Constituent letters lease--Sale #53" to "22005--Federal government--Civil service reform,", 1981 (Box 408)
    - "22010--Federal government--Civil service--General statement" to "22560--Health--FDA--Needs reform,", 1980-1981 (Box 409)
    - "22570--Health--Flouridation" to "23500--Housing,", 1981 (Box 410)
    - "23510--Housing--General statement" to "23555--Immigration--Illegal--Information file,", 1980-1981 (Box 411)
    - "23550--Housing--Task force II August 1978 Select Committee on Immigration" to "24525-International relations--1981 joint St. Patrick's Day statement," (Box 412)
  - Briefing book. Temporary workers
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 413)
    - "24525--International relations--Ireland flax trust" to "24610--International relations--Saudi Arabia arms sale,", 1981
    - "24600--International relations--Foreign aid/arms--Con" to "24677--International relations--Pakistan,", 1980-1981 (Box 414)
    - "24680--International relations--Panama Canal negotiations--Pro" to "24740--International relations--South Africa--A. McLane (1981 January),", 1980-1981 (Box 415)
    - "24740--International relations--Response to Arnnie McLane's Africa trip report" to "24760--International relations--Middle East interest groups,", 1980-1981 (Box 416)
    - "24750--International relations--Soviet Jewry" to "25655--Labor--Copies of Service Contract Act replies,", 1981 (Box 417)
    - "25655--Labor--Service Contract Act" to "28510--Social Security--Response to Reagan's cuts--Computer letter,", 1981 (Box 418)
    - "28515--Social Security--Proposed cuts" to "29500--Taxes--Inventory valuation ruling v. publishers,", 1981 (Box 419)
    - "29500--Taxes--Reform (relief for taxpayers) general statement" to "29640--Taxes--Foreign income,", 1981 (Box 420)
    - "29645--Taxes--Tuition tax breaks" to "31170--Transportation--Air controllers--Letters,", 1981 (Box 421)
    - "22035--Federal government--Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs (OFCCP)--Affirmative action statistics: Costs and benefits" to "32000--Inactive files,", 1981 (Box 422)
    - 7450--Requests--General" to "7454--Requests--Flag--R,", 1980-81 (Box 423)
    - "22035--Federal government--Federal Communications Commission affirmative action regulations" to "22035--Federal government--OFCCP affirmative action press and telephone,", 1974-1981
    - "7350--Recommendation--Burke, M. L." (Box 424)
    - "7454--Requests--Flag--S" to "8500--Washington visitor--Tour request--XYZ,", 1979-1981
  - Printed matter
    - Congressional Record reprint, The Progressive Case and the Atomic Energy Act, 1980 December 11
    - "Dear Mr. President" letter regarding AWACS package to Saudi Arabia, 1981 June 24
    - Committee hearings on Saudi arms sales, 1981
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 425)
    - "22035--Federal government--OFCCP (Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs)--Affirmative action Hatch hearings (1981 July 29)"
  - Printed matter
    - Equal employment opportunity
    - Reagan's program on regulatory relief
  - Campaign/Political file
    - George Bush presidential issue papers and campaign material, 1980
    - George Bush, 1977-1978
    - Fair presidential primary committee, 1979-1980
    - New Hampshire Dartmouth speech
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 426)
    - Reagan, 1980
    - DD press notebook, 1980
    - George Bush, 1979-1980
  - Subject file (numeric file codes). "22035--Federal government--OFCCP (Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs)--Affirmative action Hatch hearings (1981 July 16)" (Box 427)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes). "L--Law enforcement--Office of Contract Compliance informational materials"
  - Miscellany
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission
    - Defense Department Office of Federal Contract Compliance
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 428)
    - Correspondence, clippings, lists, general materials regarding campaigns, 1968-1976
    - Clippings, memoranda, etc., regarding campaigns, 1972-1976 (Box 429)
  - Subject file (numeric file codes)
    - "7008--Personal--Constituent newsletter responses general" to "7145--District office correspondence,", 1978-1979
  - Printed matter. National Journal, 1979-1980 (Box 430)
  - Sound recordings. McCloskey interviews, speeches, etc., 1974-1980. (Box 431)
    Compact sound cassettes and 1/4-inch sound tape reels
  - Printed matter (Box 432)
    - National Journal, 1978-1981
    - Congressional Quarterly Weekly Reports, 1980 (Box 433)
    - Congressional Record reprints (Box 434)
    - Published testimony of McCloskey
    - Published "Dear Mr. President" letter
    - Congressional Record reprints (Box 435)
    - Published McCloskey statements
    - Printed transcript of McCloskey interview on WETA-TV, 1971 February 16
    - Congressional Record reprints (Box 436)
    - "Dear Constituent" letters of McCloskey
  - Miscellany (Box 437)
    - Press clippings, 1970-1981
    - Ground water subcommittee report
    - J. Anderson on McCloskey, 1970-1980
    - Maritime priorities memorandum, 1978
    - Sexual assault in prisons study
  - Printed matter, 1957-1972 (Box 438)
    - Land use and land laws
    - Agricultural and urban land zoning
    - State of Hawaii land laws and land policy
    - Air pollution in San Francisco Bay Area
    - Mass media and the environment
    - Sanitary sewerage study San Mateo County
    - Mineral King
    - Conservation easements
    - Plans for Palo Alto, East Palo Alto, Foster City, San Mateo County, Skyline scenic route
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 439)
    - "21180--Environment--Environmental Protection Agency,", 1982
    - "21040--Environment--Clean Air Act,", 1982
  - Miscellany
    - Santa Clara County baylands planning, 1970
    - Weekly bulletin of the Environmental Study Conference, 1982
    - Digest of public land laws, 1968 (Box 440)
    - Future development of the San Francisco Bay Area, (1960-2020)
    - California rural legal assistance, 1969-1972
    - Riding-Hiking trails
    - Conservation Foundation printed matter, 1969
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 441)
    - Californians for McCloskey--Report of receipts and expenditures
      - 1982 May 20 - June 30
      - 1982 July 1 - September 30
    - 1982 campaign--Staff memoranda, miscellaneous fundraising, Federal Elections Commission printed matter
    - 1982 Senate Campaign. Computer tape
    - California Journal
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 442)
    - "29590--Taxes--Federal estate and gift tax" to "32100--Inactive files,", 1978
  - Printed matter, 1981-1982 (Box 443)
    - Committee prints, committee hearings, Executive branch publications, books, reports published by private organizations, etc
    - Committee prints, Executive branch publications, books, reports published by private organizations, etc. (Box 444)
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 445)
    - "20165--Energy--Chuck Hansen case (Atomic Energy Act amendment and Department of Energy classification/declassification),", 1979-1982
    - "20165--Energy--Chuck Hansen case (Atomic Energy Act amendment and Department of Energy classification/declassification),", 1979-1982 (Box 446)
    - "20165--Energy--Chuck Hansen case (Atomic Energy Act amendment and Department of Energy classification/declassification),", 1979-1982 (Box 447)
  - Miscellany (Box 448)
    - Small Business Innovation Development Act files, 1982.
      Includes McCloskey testimony in committee
    - Aircraft noise abatement (Box 449)
    - Noise pollution
    - Federal Aviation Administration
    - San Francisco Airport
    - McCloskey special correspondence, 1969 (Box 450)
    - National youth service
    - San Bruno marine reserve unit
    - Political contributions 1968 master list, 1968-1970
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 450)
    - "E--Seniority"
  - Subject file (numeric file codes)
    - "2612--1980 Congressional campaign--Quit Congress--Confidential"
  - Videorecordings
    - "Legacy of Greatness," Republican National Committee, 1982 January
    - 60 Minutes, 1981 April 5
    - McCloskey interview, "To the Point,", 1981 April 7
  - Motion picture film. Face the Nation, 1970 April 19
  - Printed matter (Box 451)
    - Hearings, reports, committee prints
      - Panama Canal, 1978-1980
      - Americans missing in Southeast Asia, 1973-1976
      - Assassination of Leo Ryan, 1979
  - Campaign/Political file--Senate campaign (Box 452)
    - Correspondence and other material, arranged by name of California county, Alameda to San Luis Obispo, 1981
    - Correspondence, including district office, Washington office, and out-of-state correspondents, 1981-1982 (Box 453)
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 454)
    - "3000--News media--Press file,", 1977
  - Campaign/Political file
    - Press releases, 1978-1979
    - Clippings, 1979
  - Subject file (numeric file codes)--Senate campaign (Box 455)
    - "2570--Campaign letter Rousselot-Lungren-Heckler-McDaniel" to "5500--Contributors--PAC,", 1981-1982
  - Campaign/Political file--Senate campaign (Box 456)
    - Correspondence and other material, arranged by name of California County, San Mateo to Yuba, 1981
    - Senate memoranda package
    - Permanent traveling campaign documents
    - McCloskey letters (position papers)
    - Exploratory committee
    - Campaign plan
    - Polls
    - Interoffice memoranda
  - Subject file (numeric file codes)--Senate campaign, 1980-1981 (Box 457)
    - "5600--Contributor--Thank you"
    - "6000--General statement of support"
    - "7000--Campaign volunteers and staff"
    - "7200--Interns"
    - "9000--Meetings"
    - "10000--Anti-McCloskey"
    - "20000--Inactive files"
  - Miscellany. Voting record for 95th Congress (Box 458)
  - Printed matter